[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Is it nice?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "nice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "How was that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "My first husband.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "first", "husband", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "ORGAN: Did you really?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "I married him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "married", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "And was he as good as you thought he would be?", "question_tokens": ["And", "was", "he", "as", "good", "as", "you", "thought", "he", "would", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Better.", "answer_tokens": ["Better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "I mean how have you kept so remarkably youthful, ladies?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "how", "have", "you", "kept", "so", "remarkably", "youthful", ",", "ladies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Refrigerators.", "answer_tokens": ["Refrigerators", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Anyone else?", "question_tokens": ["Anyone", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Fresh air.", "answer_tokens": ["Fresh", "air", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Being happy?", "question_tokens": ["Being", "happy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "You never went there?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "went", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["PBS"], "PERSON": ["Stephen Sondheim"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Angela, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Angela", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Stephen Sondheim was on PBS for his birthday celebration and he -- after the whole night, he took the microphone and he said, first you're young, then you're middle-aged, and then you're wonderful.", "answer_tokens": ["Stephen", "Sondheim", "was", "on", "PBS", "for", "his", "birthday", "celebration", "and", "he", "--", "after", "the", "whole", "night", ",", "he", "took", "the", "microphone", "and", "he", "said", ",", "first", "you", "'re", "young", ",", "then", "you", "'re", "middle-aged", ",", "and", "then", "you", "'re", "wonderful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "But is it true?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "it", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 103, "question": "When you're no longer that kind of sex symbol, what is it like for you psychologically?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "no", "longer", "that", "kind", "of", "sex", "symbol", ",", "what", "is", "it", "like", "for", "you", "psychologically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Well, I never looked at life as if I was a sex symbol so I didn't place myself in that --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "never", "looked", "at", "life", "as", "if", "I", "was", "a", "sex", "symbol", "so", "I", "did", "n't", "place", "myself", "in", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "How did you feel to hear that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "to", "hear", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Sad.", "answer_tokens": ["Sad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Yes, because it was the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "it", "was", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "What it's been like, the aging process, I guess?", "question_tokens": ["What", "it", "'s", "been", "like", ",", "the", "aging", "process", ",", "I", "guess", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "I like the aging process because I've gotten a kind of freedom from it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "the", "aging", "process", "because", "I", "'ve", "gotten", "a", "kind", "of", "freedom", "from", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "But you were this stunning operation in \"Star Trek\" and electrified the world of TV, what's it been like for you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "were", "this", "stunning", "operation", "in", "``", "Star", "Trek", "''", "and", "electrified", "the", "world", "of", "TV", ",", "what", "'s", "it", "been", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "``", "NN", "NNP", "''", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I don't speak numbers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "speak", "numbers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "And that's annoying, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "annoying", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "I told everyone my age.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "told", "everyone", "my", "age", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Have any of you lied about your age over the years?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "any", "of", "you", "lied", "about", "your", "age", "over", "the", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Oh, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["NIDENTIFIED", "FEMALE", ":", "Oh", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "What are the crucial ages for a woman to start telling fibs, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "crucial", "ages", "for", "a", "woman", "to", "start", "telling", "fibs", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "102.", "answer_tokens": ["102", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "I think that's probably true, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "probably", "true", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I think 60's brutal.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "60", "'s", "brutal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "60.", "answer_tokens": ["60", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "I mean should anyone talk about this in public?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "should", "anyone", "talk", "about", "this", "in", "public", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "NN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS"], "qSentId": 234, "question": "So talk to me about -- have you ever had it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "talk", "to", "me", "about", "--", "have", "you", "ever", "had", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Yes", "answer_tokens": ["Yes"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "And what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I think if you go to the right doctor and you -- first, if you want it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "if", "you", "go", "to", "the", "right", "doctor", "and", "you", "--", "first", ",", "if", "you", "want", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Is it pressure from men do you think that they want to see affection in women even if they get older?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "pressure", "from", "men", "do", "you", "think", "that", "they", "want", "to", "see", "affection", "in", "women", "even", "if", "they", "get", "older", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "VANS: Really in each of us I think each person does it for different reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["VANS", ":", "Really", "in", "each", "of", "us", "I", "think", "each", "person", "does", "it", "for", "different", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Do you regret it or are you pleased?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "regret", "it", "or", "are", "you", "pleased", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Did it stick around?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "stick", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "It wasn't to make him stick around.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "n't", "to", "make", "him", "stick", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What do you think, Nichelle?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", ",", "Nichelle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I think if you -- it's wonderful, it's a technology that's there for you if you need it, if you want it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "if", "you", "--", "it", "'s", "wonderful", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "technology", "that", "'s", "there", "for", "you", "if", "you", "need", "it", ",", "if", "you", "want", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nichelle"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Have you been tempted?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "tempted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "I had -- my nose broken in a car accident and I was never happy with my nose.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "--", "my", "nose", "broken", "in", "a", "car", "accident", "and", "I", "was", "never", "happy", "with", "my", "nose", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ":", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Is that a guilty run?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "guilty", "run", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "No, not -- oh, yes, I'm guilty.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "--", "oh", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "'m", "guilty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VB", ":", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "You don't?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "ICKINSON: Usually I've had girls coming to me and say -- coming crying, oh my god, I don't look like myself at all.", "answer_tokens": ["ICKINSON", ":", "Usually", "I", "'ve", "had", "girls", "coming", "to", "me", "and", "say", "--", "coming", "crying", ",", "oh", "my", "god", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "look", "like", "myself", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "''", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "IN", "EX", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Stephanie, what's your view of surgery?", "question_tokens": ["Stephanie", ",", "what", "'s", "your", "view", "of", "surgery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, I think that there's a time in an actress' life when she's making certain transitions when you're in the middle of that -- of those transitions where you're still playing leading roles but maybe there is a little puff under the eyes or a little something that's consistently catching the light and when it does it's distracting, because there -- you know, the perception of beauty, we get the perception of beauty off the cover of magazines.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "there", "'s", "a", "time", "in", "an", "actress", "'", "life", "when", "she", "'s", "making", "certain", "transitions", "when", "you", "'re", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "that", "--", "of", "those", "transitions", "where", "you", "'re", "still", "playing", "leading", "roles", "but", "maybe", "there", "is", "a", "little", "puff", "under", "the", "eyes", "or", "a", "little", "something", "that", "'s", "consistently", "catching", "the", "light", "and", "when", "it", "does", "it", "'s", "distracting", ",", "because", "there", "--", "you", "know", ",", "the", "perception", "of", "beauty", ",", "we", "get", "the", "perception", "of", "beauty", "off", "the", "cover", "of", "magazines", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Are they professional imperative, I mean, if you don't have this kind of work, particularly in America?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "professional", "imperative", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "this", "kind", "of", "work", ",", "particularly", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Pretty much.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 320, "question": "What they mean is get down to the surgeon, right?", "question_tokens": ["What", "they", "mean", "is", "get", "down", "to", "the", "surgeon", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "They mean get a little something --", "answer_tokens": ["They", "mean", "get", "a", "little", "something", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "I mean, what do you think of that picture?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "picture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I didn't need it then.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "need", "it", "then", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1965", "'66"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "When you look at that picture, what do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "that", "picture", ",", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I feel brave because it was I think 1965 or '66.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "brave", "because", "it", "was", "I", "think", "1965", "or", "'66", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "I mean it was outrageous at the time, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "was", "outrageous", "at", "the", "time", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Did you like that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I loved it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "loved", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "It's an honor and I'm not fooled by how I look and what my age is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "honor", "and", "I", "'m", "not", "fooled", "by", "how", "I", "look", "and", "what", "my", "age", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sean Connery"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Nichelle?", "question_tokens": ["Nichelle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Sean Connery.", "answer_tokens": ["Sean", "Connery", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Why Sean Connery?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "Sean", "Connery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I think he gets more beautiful as he gets older.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "gets", "more", "beautiful", "as", "he", "gets", "older", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sean Connery"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Have you met, Sean?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", ",", "Sean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sean"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "And did you get anywhere with it or not?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "you", "get", "anywhere", "with", "it", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "I got as close as I could.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "as", "close", "as", "I", "could", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny Depp"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Linda, how about you?", "question_tokens": ["Linda", ",", "how", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "RP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Johnny Depp for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Johnny", "Depp", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Little pirate toy boy, huh?", "question_tokens": ["Little", "pirate", "toy", "boy", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "I don't think there's anything about him that's a toy boy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "anything", "about", "him", "that", "'s", "a", "toy", "boy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Have you met Johnny Depp?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "Johnny", "Depp", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny Depp"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Would you like to?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 434, "question": "If he's watching, have you got a message for him?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "'s", "watching", ",", "have", "you", "got", "a", "message", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Well, I'm happy he's married and he's got his life --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "happy", "he", "'s", "married", "and", "he", "'s", "got", "his", "life", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "I think you're happy about that at all, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'re", "happy", "about", "that", "at", "all", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Can't you jump to Stephanie?", "question_tokens": ["Ca", "n't", "you", "jump", "to", "Stephanie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "No --", "answer_tokens": ["No", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stephanie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Who could tell me stories and have that -- you know, brilliant.", "answer_tokens": ["Who", "could", "tell", "me", "stories", "and", "have", "that", "--", "you", "know", ",", "brilliant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "You wouldn't want sex for Johnny Depp?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "n't", "want", "sex", "for", "Johnny", "Depp", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "No, no, it isn't -- it wasn't -- the choice was not based on sex.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "it", "is", "n't", "--", "it", "was", "n't", "--", "the", "choice", "was", "not", "based", "on", "sex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny Depp"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Could you imagine?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "imagine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Waking up to Winston Churchill with a cigar?", "question_tokens": ["Waking", "up", "to", "Winston", "Churchill", "with", "a", "cigar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Winston Churchill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Holden"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Stephanie, how about you?", "question_tokens": ["Stephanie", ",", "how", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "RP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Gosh, well, my first thought of course was Bill Holden.", "answer_tokens": ["Gosh", ",", "well", ",", "my", "first", "thought", "of", "course", "was", "Bill", "Holden", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Russia"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "He was only about 5'3\", wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "only", "about", "5'3", "''", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CD", "''", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Maybe I could have convinced him not to go on to Russia.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "I", "could", "have", "convinced", "him", "not", "to", "go", "on", "to", "Russia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Who's been the great love of your life?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "been", "the", "great", "love", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Frank.", "answer_tokens": ["Frank", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Frank Sinatra?", "question_tokens": ["Frank", "Sinatra", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sinatra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Why frank?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "frank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Because he was smashing.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "was", "smashing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Was he as great as I imagined him to be?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "as", "great", "as", "I", "imagined", "him", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Was he good with women, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "good", "with", "women", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Not all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "You know this for sure?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "this", "for", "sure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Yes, I know this for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "know", "this", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "In your case who would be the great love of your life?", "question_tokens": ["In", "your", "case", "who", "would", "be", "the", "great", "love", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "I don't want to answer that because he was the great love of my life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "answer", "that", "because", "he", "was", "the", "great", "love", "of", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "When you have that kind of love, and then you lose it, do you -- can you ever get it back from anybody else?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "have", "that", "kind", "of", "love", ",", "and", "then", "you", "lose", "it", ",", "do", "you", "--", "can", "you", "ever", "get", "it", "back", "from", "anybody", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "ICHOLS: I don't know that that's so.", "answer_tokens": ["ICHOLS", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "that", "'s", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Who would be the love of your life?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "be", "the", "love", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Well, I've been fortunate in that I loved my first husband so much, but I would say Yanni --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "fortunate", "in", "that", "I", "loved", "my", "first", "husband", "so", "much", ",", "but", "I", "would", "say", "Yanni", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "-- would be the love of my life.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "would", "be", "the", "love", "of", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William Holden"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Stefanie?", "question_tokens": ["Stefanie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Oh, well, of course, I think that William Holden came into my life at a time in my life and in his life that was an extremely strong connection.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "well", ",", "of", "course", ",", "I", "think", "that", "William", "Holden", "came", "into", "my", "life", "at", "a", "time", "in", "my", "life", "and", "in", "his", "life", "that", "was", "an", "extremely", "strong", "connection", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBD", ",", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Were you aware at the time of how significant it was going to be?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "aware", "at", "the", "time", "of", "how", "significant", "it", "was", "going", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "When he actually kissed me, the director says, cut, cut, cut.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "he", "actually", "kissed", "me", ",", "the", "director", "says", ",", "cut", ",", "cut", ",", "cut", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Was it as hard as it seems now looking back on that era?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "as", "hard", "as", "it", "seems", "now", "looking", "back", "on", "that", "era", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "You've asked the wrong person.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "asked", "the", "wrong", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "I've had a career that should never be because I didn't want to be an actress.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "had", "a", "career", "that", "should", "never", "be", "because", "I", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "be", "an", "actress", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Oh, no, you had a gun, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", ",", "you", "had", "a", "gun", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "I had every gun (INAUDIBLE).", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "every", "gun", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Did you feel like you were making a bit of a stand here?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "like", "you", "were", "making", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "stand", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "I just felt exhausted.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "felt", "exhausted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "When you see the young actresses today, do you think they have it easier, really, than you had it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "young", "actresses", "today", ",", "do", "you", "think", "they", "have", "it", "easier", ",", "really", ",", "than", "you", "had", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "When you have to lead your life in a goldfish bowl of fame, how much harder is it when you go through the tough times in life, do you think, to be famous and going through it with everybody having an eye on what's going on?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "have", "to", "lead", "your", "life", "in", "a", "goldfish", "bowl", "of", "fame", ",", "how", "much", "harder", "is", "it", "when", "you", "go", "through", "the", "tough", "times", "in", "life", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "to", "be", "famous", "and", "going", "through", "it", "with", "everybody", "having", "an", "eye", "on", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "Now you can't breathe without having everything out there.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "you", "ca", "n't", "breathe", "without", "having", "everything", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ":", ":", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "(voice-over): Yes, really.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "voice-over", ")", ":", "Yes", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "Is that what's bugging you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "'s", "bugging", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "No, that's not what's bugging me.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "what", "'s", "bugging", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 800, "question": "I mean, are you friends or not really?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "are", "you", "friends", "or", "not", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 801, "answer": "There's getting along and friends.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "getting", "along", "and", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 804, "question": "How can you ever be friendly with anyone again after that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "you", "ever", "be", "friendly", "with", "anyone", "again", "after", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 805, "answer": "Well, that's what I mean.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "I", "mean", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barbara Stanwick"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Are you a bit fiery in real life?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "bit", "fiery", "in", "real", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "Barbara Stanwick taught me to do stunts when I did \"Big Valley.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Barbara", "Stanwick", "taught", "me", "to", "do", "stunts", "when", "I", "did", "``", "Big", "Valley", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 816, "question": "ORGAN: Did you use it on a man before?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "you", "use", "it", "on", "a", "man", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 817, "answer": "I never slapped anybody except on \"Dynasty\" ever, ever.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "slapped", "anybody", "except", "on", "``", "Dynasty", "''", "ever", ",", "ever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "And when you actually do those things, would you actually whack each other or not?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "you", "actually", "do", "those", "things", ",", "would", "you", "actually", "whack", "each", "other", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 834, "question": "-- try and get one through just to, you know, assert your authority?", "question_tokens": ["--", "try", "and", "get", "one", "through", "just", "to", ",", "you", "know", ",", "assert", "your", "authority", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "CC", "VB", "CD", "IN", "RB", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 835, "answer": "That would not work well.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "would", "not", "work", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Blue Angels"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 856, "question": "Linda?", "question_tokens": ["Linda", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 857, "answer": "When I flew with the Blue Angels.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "flew", "with", "the", "Blue", "Angels", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 868, "question": "And then you're sick, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "you", "'re", "sick", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 869, "answer": "I mean, no, I didn't get sick.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "no", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "get", "sick", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 876, "question": "Nichelle?", "question_tokens": ["Nichelle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 877, "answer": "I think of three in my whole life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "of", "three", "in", "my", "whole", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Thousand Oaks"]}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "Where were you?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "In Thousand Oaks, out where it was dark.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "Thousand", "Oaks", ",", "out", "where", "it", "was", "dark", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 905, "question": "Is it over?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "over", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 906, "answer": "I'm afraid it's over.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "afraid", "it", "'s", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]